[{"answer": "You're all wet and muddy. Why don't I hang those up to dry", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm propositioning you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I am not", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Easy for you, you've got my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Sorry", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The best wine is beer", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What a relief. I'm that place. You", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Workin' late, huh? my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Damn. Will you look at that tonsil hockey", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You've been staring at him all night. You got a thing for him, or what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'd prefer not. This could get bad", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Actually, I'm hoping he's got one for me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What're you givin' me?", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "\"Caaalm Down?!!!!!", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No. She's just visiting", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Exactly. He was a girl", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Would you rather she was attracted to me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Where'd you learn to speak Italian", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Have you been", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's not what you think", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What about him", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes! So you can just go fuck yourself.", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What if he does? Do you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What if he does? Do you", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And you're a girl", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " I'm not supposed to be", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Is that what you think?! NO", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Everything reminded me of him. So, I came here, half way round the world to forget. Then created this place, just like the one where we met", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You being a guy too", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "He can't handle this. Us. He can't handle who he is", "docId": "Zerophilia.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Or him being a girl", "qsentId": 32}]